Guide to the Austin Dobson Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Herman W. Liebert Collection of Austin Dobson, 1866-1930; Series I; 7.59; (19 boxes)
  - Poems: Individual
    - "Goodnight Babette!" gallery proof of poem., undated (Box 7)
      Heavily corrected by the author for publication in a periodical, 1 page.
    - In the porch: reverie of a summers-day stoic: autograph poem., undated (Box 7)
    - [Invocation to Mammon]: autograph poem.., no year July (Box 7)
    - Last despatch: autograph poem (fragment)., undated (Box 7)
    - Last page: autograph (not Austin Dobson's hand) of poem, signed by Austin Dobson., undated (Box 7)
    - Leaf from a love story: autograph poem., undated (Box 7)
    - Learned sir!: autograph poem., undated (Box 7)
    - Lytell Geste of Sir Pleindamour: autograph poem., undated (Box 7)
    - Molly Trefusis: autograph poem, signed and dated., 1875 June 5 (Box 7)
    - Molly Trefusis: autograph poem., undated (Box 7)
    - Natural selection: autograph poem., undated (Box 7)
    - Old Magazine: typescript of poem., undated (Box 7)
    - Old Magazine: corrected typescript., undated (Box 7)
    - Old Magazine: autograph., 1910 January 1 (Box 7)
    - Old Sedan Chair: autograph of poem., undated (Box 7)
    - Old Sedan-Chair: autograph of poem., 1883 November 2 (Box 7)
    - [On a fan that belonged to the Marquise de Pompadour]: autograph poem, incomplete., 1878 August 9 (Box 7)
    - [On a fan that belonged to the Marquise de Pompadour]: proof., undated (Box 7)
    - On an egoist: autograph poem., undated (Box 7)
    - On London stories: corrected proof., undated (Box 7)
    - On the belfry tower: corrected proof of poem., undated (Box 7)
    - On the shelf: manuscript poem, signed., undated (Box 7)
    - Peacock on the wall: autograph poem., undated (Box 7)
    - 'Persicos odi': autograph poem., undated (Box 7)
    - The Poet's Seat: An Idyll of the Suburbs: autograph poem, signed., undated (Box 7)
      3 pages.
      With: Dobson, Austin. Autograph letter signed to J. Eliot Brown. 1890 January 22. 1 page and envelope.
    - Polycaste: autograph poem., 1868 March 21 (Box 7)
    - Poor Miss Tox: proof, undated (Box 7)
    - Pot-pourri: autograph poem., undated (Box 7)
    - Pot-pourri: autograph poem., undated (Box 7)
    - Prodigals: corrected proof., undated (Box 7)
      Originally named "The Beggars"
      With: An Antique Gem
    - [Prologue to 'A Bookman's Budget']: autograph poem., 1916 June 15 (Box 7)
    - Proverbs in Porcelain: corrected proofs., 1893 (Box 7)
    - Proverbs in Porcelain: autograph poem., undated (Box 7)
    - R. L. S. In Memoriam: autograph poem., 1901 January 7 (Box 7)
    - Rank and File (South Africa 1900-1901): autograph poem. (Box 7)
    - Riddle: corrected proof., 1915 November 23 (Box 7)
    - Le Roman de la Rose: autograph poem, signed., undated (Box 7)
    - Rose leaves: corrected extract., undated (Box 7)
    - Rose leaves: A Kiss...: autograph poem., 1886 July 31 (Box 7)
    - Simple Life: autograph poem., undated (Box 7)
    - Sine me liber, ibis in urbem: autograph poem., 1916 October 23 (Box 7)
    - Song of the sea wind: autograph poem., 1889 November 28 (Box 7)
    - Sunrise before the battle: autograph poem, incomplete., undated (Box 7)
    - Tale of Polypheme: autograph poem, incomplete., undated (Box 8)
    - The Dear Old Tune: autograph poem., 1874 (Box 8)
      1874 Saturday Journa l but apparently never reprinted.
      Not in Collected Poems.
    - Threescore and ten: corrected proof of poem., undated (Box 8)
    - To an enquiring editor: autograph poem., 1918 (Box 8)
    - To a Lyric Poet, 1920 January 6 - February 20 (Box 8)
      Autograph manuscript, signed, with corrections of poem. 2 pages.
      With: typescript with corrections and leaf of autograph manuscript, signed, attached. 3 pages. Typescript carbon with corrections. 2 pages.
    - To a Publisher, By way of preface: corrected typescript of poem., undated (Box 8)
    - To Arthur Waugh (1890-1916): autograph poem., 1916 December 5 - 8 (Box 8)
    - To John Hicks, Esquire: autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - To Posthumus - in reversion: autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - To Stella at Home: autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - To Thestylis: autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - Under Which King?: autograph poem., 1903 March (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "Ah! too gentle... ": autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "All wise, all great, whose ancient plan...": autograph poem., 1904 September 9 (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "And some will dance": autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "Chime out ye foxgloves from your speckled throats": autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "Friend, for we sure may call him friend": autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "How is love born": autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "Is peace so peaceful": autograph poem., 1895 March 19 (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "The man was elderly and not aesthetic": 2 autograph poems., undated (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "Men change the hour, Not so my deal": autograph poem., 1916 July 24 (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "Muse, o ye warrior": autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "No more I think": autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "No, on the whole": autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "Nor while thy verse shew": autograph poem., 1920 September 6 (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "Of all things delicate": autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "Oh, love's but a dance": autograph poem., 1898 April 19 (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "Recount and welcome your misdeeds": autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "So he wrote the old bard": autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "The world's a sorry spot": autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "'Tis so embarassing": autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "To this there followed a Chrysoprasus": autograph poem., 1876 October 3 (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "Vogue la galere": autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "Well, one day-- it had rained for long...": autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - [Untitled Poem] "When I woke": autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - Virgin with the bells: autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - "Vitas hinnuleo": autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - Vitas Hinnuleo...: corrected proof., undated (Box 8)
    - Wanton Clerk: autograph poem., 1900 January 1 (Box 8)
      to W.J.H.
    - When Finis comes: autograph poem., 1918 January 19 (Box 8)
    - Who haunt the chambers of the great: autograph poem., undated (Box 8)
    - William Makepeace Thackeray, 1911 (Box 8)
      (1) First separate edition, one of 20 copies, inscribed by Austin Dobson to R. U. Johnson.
      (2) Corrected proof for Cornhill Magazine, July 1911.
      With: autograph letter, signed, from Dobson to an unidentified recipient. 1913 January 23.
      (3) 2 corrected typescripts, signed. One dated 1911 April 12. 3 pages each.
    - Yolande le Fay: autograph manuscript of an unpublished poem., [1867] (Box 8)
      5 pages.
      With: manuscript note by Alban Dobson on wrapper.
  - Essays and Prose
    - [Alexander Pope essay]: incomplete autograph manuscript., undated (Box 9)
    - Appendix A: Carmontelle's Transparencies: autograph manuscript., undated (Box 9)
      Possibly meant for Bookman's Budget.
    - Appendix B: Exhibitions of the Eidophusikon...: autograph manuscript., undated (Box 9)
    - Appendix B: Death of the Bailli de Suffren: autograph manuscript, undated (Box 9)
      Possibly (originally) meant for Bookman's Budget.
    - At "Tully's Head", 1893 July 14 (Box 9)
    - [Biography of John Zoffany for the Dictionary of National Biography]: galley proof., 1900 February 19 (Box 9)
    - Biography [pertaining to Oliver Goldsmith]: autograph manuscript., undated (Box 9)
    - [Biography of William Cosmo Monkhouse for DNB Supplies January 1901 - December 1911]: autograph manuscript., undated (Box 9)
    - Books and talks: autograph manuscript., undated (Box 9)
    - By ways of book-illustration. "Jacob Cats.": incomplete autograph manuscript., undated (Box 9)
    - Casual Causerie:, undated (Box 9)
    - David Wilkie, undated (Box 9)
    - Day at Strawberry Hill, undated (Box 9)
    - [de Castro]: autograph note signed, 1916 September 19 (Box 10)
    - De Libris, 1908 (Box 10)
    - Denis Duval, undated (Box 10)
    - [Eighteenth century]: corrected proof, undated (Box 10)
    - Eighteenth century essays: autograph, undated (Box 10)
    - Eighteenth century essays. Dedication: autograph, undated (Box 10)
    - Eighteenth century vignettes, General Index: autograph, undated (Box 10)
    - Fanny Burney (Madame d'Arblay). Chapter III: Story of "Evelina": proof, 1903 September 4 (Box 10)
    - Fielding find., 1912 January 26 (Box 10)
    - Fielding's Tomb: autograph, undated (Box 10)
    - Fine Lady's Journal: autograph (incomplete), undated (Box 10)
    - Four Frenchwomen., undated (Box 10)
    - General Oglethorpe: autograph, undated (Box 10)
    - [Greeting] "To a friend": autograph, undated (Box 10)
    - Handbook of English literature., 1874 (Box 10)
    - Henry Fielding: autograph, undated (Box 10)
    - [Henry Fielding essay]: incomplete autograph, undated (Box 10)
    - [How Dr. Johnson wrote his dictionary]: autograph, undated (Box 10)
    - Jacques Callot: autograph, undated (Box 11)
      Manuscript of a very early paper, apparently unpublished.
    - Later essays: autograph, 1917 December 28 - 1918 August 30 (Box 11)
      Accompanied by typescript.
    - Life of Oliver Goldsmith, appendix: autograph, undated (Box 11)
    - Mme. Vigee-Lebrun: typescript, undated (Box 11)
      National Review. December 1909. Typescript corrected by the author.
      Reprinted in Old Kensington Palace 1910.
    - On Certain Quotations in Walton's Angler: typescript, 1901 January (Box 11)
      Printed in pamphlet(?) "The Library," edited by J. Y. W. Macalister.
    - Percy and Goldsmith: autograph essay, [April 1909] (Box 11)
      Essay in manuscript, but incomplete.
      First approved in National Review April 1909 and was subsequently reprinted in Austin Dobson's Old Kensington's Palace 1910.
    - "The Pursuits of Literature," and its author: autograph manuscript., 1913 February 10 (Box 11)
    - [Samuel Richardson] corrected proofs, incomplete., undated (Box 12)
    - [Samuel Richardson]: autograph manucript, incomplete., undated (Box 12)
    - [Samuel Richardson]: autograph manuscript, incomplete., undated (Box 12)
    - Samuel Richardson [Chapter II: Pamela...]: galley proof., 1902 January 2 (Box 12)
    - Scott: autograph manuscript., undated (Box 12)
      With poem "To Dovil-Matilda"
    - Portion of essay "Chinese Shadows" in Sidewalk Stories: autograph manuscript., undated (Box 12)
      In French.
    - Sidewalk Studies: General Index, 1902 (Box 12)
    - Stories of the Stage. II. The Long Strike: autograph manuscript., undated (Box 12)
    - Sufferance of fools: typescript., undated (Box 12)
    - [unidentified essay]: autograph manuscript, incomplete., undated (Box 12)
    - [unidentified essay]: autograph manuscript, incomplete., undated (Box 12)
    - [unidentified essay]: autograph manuscript, incomplete., undated (Box 12)
    - [unidentified essay]: autograph manuscript,incomplete., undated (Box 12)
    - Victor Hugo: autograph manuscript., undated (Box 12)
      Signed with initials.
      14 pages.
      In blue paper wrappers.
      On page 15: The Bell-Buoy: autograph poem, in pencil
    - William Hogarth: autograph manuscript., 1890 (Box 12)
      Dictionary of National Biography entry.
    - William Lisle Bowles: autograph manuscript., undated (Box 12)
  - Introductions, Lectures, Prefaces, Reviews
    - [Introduction to John Gay section of Ward's English Poets ]: autograph manuscript., undated (Box 13)
    - Introduction to Hunt's Old Court Suburb: corrected proof., 1901 October 16 (Box 13)
    - Introduction by Austin Dobson to Boswell's Life of Samuel Johnson: autograph manuscript., 1901. (Box 13)
    - Introduction to Locker's London Lyrics: autograph manuscript., 1904 October (Box 13)
    - Introduction to Locker's London Lyrics: autograph manuscript., undated (Box 13)
      With Notes by Austin Dobson for his edition of Locker-Lampson's London Lyrics, 1904. (Partly in Mrs. Dobson's hand)
    - [Introduction to the Matthew Prior section of Ward's English Poets ]: autograph manuscript., undated (Box 13)
    - Introduction to the Selected Poems of Matthew Prior: autograph manuscript & corrected proof., 1888 (Box 13)
      Short essay first printed in The Princeton Review, November 1888.
      Expanded and revised as the Introduction to Prior's Poems. Kegan, Paul. 1889.
      Finally reproduced in Eighteenth Century Vignettes, Series III.
    - Introduction to Matthew Prior in Parliament Library, 1889 (Box 13)
      Reprinted in Eighteenth Century Vignettes, Series III. 1894.
    - [Introduction to Shakespeare's Twelfth Night ]: corrected proofs., 1902 November 29 (Box 13)
    - Introduction to Steele Selections, undated (Box 13)
      Early autograph manuscript, incomplete.
    - Introduction to [unidentified work]: autograph manuscript., undated (Box 13)
    - Introduction to [unidentified work]: incomplete autograph manuscript., undated (Box 13)
    - [Lectures] autograph manuscript of five lectures., undated (Box 13)
      13 pages, in marbled paper wrappers.
      Contents: Lecture I; Lecture 4, The Greek Theatres; Lecture V178, Aeschylus; Lecture 8, Euripides.
      Possibly written while Dobson was at Strasbourg Gymnasium.
    - Preface to Diary and Letters, 1778-1840, of Madame D'Arblay, undated (Box 13)
    - Preface for [selections for the poetry of Robert Herrick]: autograph manuscript., undated (Box 13)
    - Preface to Robinson Crusoe, 1883 (Box 13)
    - Prefatory note to [Samuel Richardson's Pamela ]: galley proof., 1902 (Box 13)
      With many corrections in his hand on three separate sheets. "The prefatory note" to a new American edition of Richardson's Pamela.
    - Prologue to Abbey's edition of She stoops to conquer: autograph manuscript., undated (Box 13)
    - [Review of the Age of Johnson by Thomas Secombe]: autograph manuscript., undated (Box 13)
    - [Review of a book about the Chavalier D'Eon]: autograph manuscript., [ca. 1865] (Box 13)
      7 pages, in a blue paper wrapper.
    - [Review of the Life and Works of Joseph Wright ]: autograph manuscript., undated (Box 13)
    - Review of Songs of Many Seasons: autograph manuscript., undated (Box 13)
  - Proofs (Box 13)
    - Edwards' "Canons of Criticism": proof., undated (Box 14)
    - Edwards' "Canons of Criticism": proof, 1917 August 6 (Box 14)
    - An Eighteenth Century Hippocrates: proof., 1917 November 8 (Box 14)
    - Sir John Hawkins, Knight: proof., undated (Box 14)
    - Sir John Hawkins, Knight: proof., 1910 January 17 (Box 14)
    - Laureate Whitehead: proof., 1910 March 12 (Box 14)
    - Old Kensington Place: proof., 1909 September 4 (Box 14)
    - Rejected Addresses: proof., 1874 (Box 14)
    - Rejected Addresses: printed copy., 1874 July 18 (Box 14)
  - Notes
    - Charing Cross [Research notes]: autograph notebook., [1883-1884] (Box 15)
    - General Oglethorpe [Research notes]: autograph notebook., [1898-1899] (Box 15)
    - Geographical notes "et ego militair": autograph notebook., 1862-1863 (Box 15)
      With maps.
      Possibly the earliest prose manuscript of Austin Dobson in existence.
    - Johnson in London: autograph notebook., undated (Box 15)
      Subheadings: Introduction, Houses, Churches, Places of Amusement, Friends' houses, Taverns and coffee houses
    - Lady Hervey at Ickworth [Research notes]: autograph manuscript., [1894-1895] (Box 15)
      Notes on 1700-1768.
    - Mrs. Lenox [Research Notes]: autograph manuscript., [1891-1892] (Box 15)
    - Life and writings of Beaumarchais [Research Notes]: 2 autograph notebooks., [1883-1884] (Box 15)
    - Dr. Mead [Research notes]: autograph notebook., [1892-1893] (Box 15)
    - [Prose Writers]: manuscript notes., undated (Box 16)
    - Samuel Richardson [Research notes]: 7 autograph notebooks., undated (Box 16)
    - Sir W. Chambers [Research notes]: autograph notebook., [1907-1908] (Box 16)
    - Stothard [Research notes]: autograph notebook., [1891-1892] (Box 16)
    - Vauxhall [Research notes]: autograph notebook., [1884-1885] (Box 16)
      1st in a series of 18th century vignettes.
    - Whitehall [Research notes]: autograph notebook., [1883-1884] (Box 16)
    - [Works by others]: research notes. (Box 16)
  - William Hogarth Research Materials
    - [The Art of William Hogarth]: autograph notebook., undated (Box 17)
    - Explication Estampes d'horgarths: notes on the art of William Hogarth., undated (Box 17)
    - Autograph notes concerning the art of William Hogarth., undated (Box 17)
    - Correspondence regarding the art of William Hogarth., undated (Box 17)
    - Correspondence regarding the art of William Hogarth., undated (Box 17)
    - Press cuttings regarding the art of William Hogarth., undated (Box 17)
    - Press cuttings regarding the art of William Hogarth., undated (Box 17)
    - Printed copies of the art of William Hogarth., undated (Box 17)
    - Exhibition catalogues, undated (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous
    - At the sign of the lyre, quote from page 137: autograph, 1905 February 13 (Box 18)
    - Bookman's Budget: autograph & corrected proof, incomplete, undated (Box 18)
      97 pages of manuscript, corrected typescript, and corrected proofs (some not used)
    - Civil Service Geography: autograph manuscript, incomplete, undated (Box 18)
      47 pages and 10 pages of corrected proofs and 1 map.
      Drawn by Austin Dobson.
    - G. Gregory Smith: autograph note, signed., 1904 May 31 (Box 18)
    - Clark, Reginald: The Ladies of St. James Song., [1905] (Box 18)
      Words by Austin Dobson.
      Music by Reginald Clarke.
      New York: Boosey and Company; London: Elkin and Company, Limited.
    - Horace: De Arte Poetica., undated (Box 18)
      Annotated by Austin Dobson.
    - Papers (addition); correspondence, notes and printed materials, undated (Box 18)
    - Pocket address book, 1876 January 24 (Box 18)
      Begun 24 January 1876 and kept for at least 2 years.
      2 x 3.5 inches.
      With presentation inscription from Christopher Dobson, his grandson.
    - Poetry Review: Order Form, undated (Box 18)
    - Portraits (12) of Austin Dobson, undated (Box 18)
    - Prospectus, undated (Box 18)
      Taken from a bound book.
  - Oversize
    - Thomson, Hugh: 2 pen and ink sketches for Austin Dobson, 1892, 1899 (Box Oversize 19)
      Preliminary sketch for title or ½ title, Ballad of Beau Brocade, by Austin Dobson, 1892. Not used. Gift of Hugh Thomson to Austin Dobson.
      Triplet, character in C. Read's Peg Woffington, ill. London, 1899. Not used in book. Hugh Thomson's gift to Austin Dobson.
    - Album of Austin Dobson., undated (Box Oversize 19)
      Album assembled by the Reverend C. C. Dobson, Austin Dobson's son, containing: Austin Dobson bookplates, portraits, family photographs, clippings from newspapers and magazines, 2 autograph letters, 1 corrected proof, 21 manuscript poems, and heavily corrected and annotated tearsheets of Beau Brocade from Hood's Comic Almanac, 1877.
    - Manuscript Poems, undated (Box Oversize 19)
      Together with a manuscript poem and corrected proof of an article on Henry Austin Dobson by Sir Edmund Gosse, C. B., LL.D.
- Other Austin Dobson Papers, 1875-1920; Series II; 0.42; (1 box)
  Manuscripts in alphabetical order, followed by letters, mostly in alphabeticaly order.
  Contents include discretely acquired manuscripts and letters by Austin Dobson. For further information, consult the appropriate curator.
  - Eight Autograph Manuscript Poems, undated (Box 20)
    The ballad a la mode | Dawns | Hesperides | The Mosque of the Caliph | On the belfry | The prayer of the swine to Circe | A Roman round-robin | Rondel
  - "To an unknown bust in the British Museum", 1920 March 22 (Box 20)
    Manuscript of two stanzas from a discarded version of the poem. S.I.: 1913 March 22.
    Accompanied by autograph address to Whitslaw Saunders, Esquire. Postmarked 1920 March 23.
  - 30 brief autograph letters, signed, and autograph cards, signed, to various correspondents, Ealing, W. [etc.]., 1876-1912. (Box 20)
  - Autograph letter signed to [William Cox Bennett]., 1875 July 6 (Box 20)
  - Autograph letter, signed, to Mr. Dean., 1891 October 5 (Box 20)
  - Autograph letter, signed, to John Paul De Castro., 1916 December 19 (Box 20)
    Concerning Henry Fielding.
  - Autograph letter, signed, to J.W.Ford, 1894 December 12 (Box 20)
  - Autograph letter, signed, to Mr. Irishfield., 1917 March 22 (Box 20)
    Ealing.
    Concerning the restrictions of arthritis, works of literature, and the Great War.
  - Autograph letter, signed, to Isaac Irving, Esquire., 1911 February 28 (Box 20)
    Presumably concerning Irving's professed desire to set a poem of Dobson's to music.
    Removed from Dobson's A Paladin of Philanthropy London, 1899.
  - Autograph letter, signed, and autograph postcard, signed, to R[obert] U[nderwood] Johnson., [19]09 November 27, 1913 April 19 (Box 20)
  - Autograph note signed to Mr. Lillis., 1917 November 25 (Box 20)
    Regretting that he can give no information about Mrs. Radcliffe.
  - Autograph letter, signed to "Dear Madam.", [18]99 April 16 (Box 20)
  - 3 autograph letters, signed, to Archibald Marshall., 1907 April 18 - 1908 February 6 (Box 20)
    Concerning Dobson's suitability to journalism and a book of Marshall's.
  - Autograph letter, signed, to Mr. Marston., 1891 July 7 (Box 20)
  - Autograph letter, signed, to "My dear Matthews.", 1881 June 25 (Box 20)
    Board of Trade.
  - Autograph letter, signed, to Mrs. Munby., 1910 February 3 (Box 20)
    Offering condolences on the death of her brother-in-law Arthur J. Munby, the poet.
  - Autograph letter, signed, to Mr. Osgood., 1887 March 4 (Box 20)
  - Autograph letter, signed, to [Alfred] Parsons and "Abbey.", 1884 March 15 (Box 20)
  - Autograph letter, signed, to Clinton Scollard, 1887 December 22 (Box 20)
    Concerning Scollard's poetry.
  - Autograph letter, signed, to Mr. Watt., 1876 June 13 (Box 20)
  - Autograph letter, signed, to Mr. Watt., 1876 October 10 (Box 20)
- 1986 Addition to the Herman W. Liebert Collection of Austin Dobson, 1902-1921; 3.71; (5 boxes)
  Papers (addition): bound proofs, clippings, and other printed ephemera and Alban Dobson's index cards.
  - Printed material including ephemera, 1902-1921 (Box 21)
  - Printed material including ephemera, 1902-1921 (Box 22)
  - Printed material including ephemera, 1902-1921 (Box 23)
  - Printed material including ephemera, 1902-1921 (Box 24 (Oversize))
  - Austin Dobson file card box, undated (Box 25)